earthfare.com 2012-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Earth Fare, the healthy supermarket

At Earth Fare, we recognize that your privacy is important. This Privacy Policy covers the Earth Fare website. We may also post supplementary privacy notices and information on our website.

Earth Fare adheres to the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Program.

## Types of Information Gathered

When you use our website, we may gather the following types of information: 

  * Information You Provide to Earth Fare – When you sign up for an Earth Fare account or promotion that requires you to register your account, we may ask you for your personal information, which could include your name, email address, user name, etc. We may combine the information that you submit under your account with information from other Earth Fare services or third parties in an effort to improve not only your experience, but our services as well. For certain services, you may be able to opt out of combining these services. We may also conduct voluntary surveys and polls. 
  * Information Provided When You Log into Earth Fare’s Website – When you log into Earth Fare’s website, our servers will automatically record the information that your browser sends to us, creating a server log. These logs may include the following information: your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * Information You Send to Earth Fare – When you send communications to Earth Fare, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

## Email Addresses

Earth Fare asks for your email address on our subscription. This allows us to provide you with email communications. Earth Fare does not sell, rent, or lend the email addresses of our subscribers or visitors to the Website. You may opt out of our email communications at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe or remove link located at the bottom of all our email communications. You may also call us at 828-281-4800 or email us at [information@earthfare.com](mailto:information@earthfare.com).

## Use of Cookies

When you visit Earth Fare’s website, we may send one or more cookies – small files containing a string of characters – to your computer, mobile device, or other machine. This gives your browser a unique identifier, and we can identify you with this cookie. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and your experience, including for storing your preferences, improving search results, and tracking how people search.

## Viewing and Updating Personal Information

Earth Fare wants you to be able to access, edit, update, or even delete your personal information, unless that information is required by law or business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves by a user name, password, or other identifying information and identify the information that they wish to access, change, edit, or delete. Earth Fare has the right to decline any process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical, or would relate to restricted information.

## Earth Fare’s Use of Your Information

We will provide any information that we are required by law to share.

## Security

Earth Fare takes steps to protect you against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your data. We will periodically review our data collection methods, storage security processes, and other security measures to guard against unauthorized access to your personal data.

Access to your information is restricted to Earth Fare employees, contractors, and agents on a need-to-know basis. These people are bound to confidentiality agreements and may be subject to disciplinary actions if they do not abide by these guidelines.

Earth Fare uses industry-standard security software and systems.

## Links

Our website may contain links to other websites. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to these websites, so you should read the Privacy Policy for each such linked website before using it.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).

## If You Have Questions or Need More Information

If you have any questions or need more information about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at information@earthfare.com or to write to us at: 

Earth Fare  
Attn: Privacy Matters  
145 Cane Creek Industrial DriveSuite 150  
Fletcher, NC 28732
